Contact

lustalynn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/natashaluster-msn-cnor-4798b7126 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Surgery

Leadership Healthcare Management

Honors-Awards

Wall of Excellence Integrity
Leadership Trendsetter Award
Honorable Mention Nursing
Leadership
Wall of Excellence

Emerging Leader of the Year

Natasha Luster, MSN, CNOR

Nurse Manager Surgical Services at Miami Valley Hospital Dayton, Ohio Area

Summary

Experienced Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Nursing, Endoscopy, Surgery, and Healthcare Management. Strong support professional with a MSN focused in Nursing Administration from Urbana University.

Experience

Premier Health Partners 13 years 11 months

Nurse Manager Surgical Services at Miami Valley Hospital November 2014 - Present (5 years 9 months) Miami Valley

Nurse Manager Endoscopy at Miami Valley Hospital September 2012 - May 2015 (2 years 9 months)

Associate Nurse Manager 6 South Advanced Care and Neuro Intensive Care

2010 - September 2012 (2 years)

RN

September 2006 - 2010 (4 years)

Miami Valley

Education

Urbana University

MSN, Nursing Administration · (2014 - 2017)

Ohio University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012)

Community Hospital School of Nursing

Diploma of Nursing · (2006)